[music]
[music] You've reached the voicemail of
Britney Schmidt.
>> Please leave your message after the
tone.
[music]
>> Hello, Briner. This is your pops
calling. Um, I just want to
wish you good luck on your new on your
show and uh maybe you could tone it down
a little bit. uh make it a little more
familyfriendly.
Um I don't want people to think that I
raised common street trash.
So
with that, uh good luck on the show and
I'll talk to you soon. Bye. [music]
>> Ladies and gentlemen, please put your
hands together FOR BRITNEY SCHMIDT.
>> [music]
[cheering]
[music]
>> WHAT'S UP, CHICAGO?
[cheering]
>> You guys, I AM A DIVORCE.
>> [cheering]
>> IT IS A very fancy word for failure.
[laughter]
I was married for five years. And uh
when your marriage starts to hit the
skids, people start to say really
useless [\h__\h] to try and make you feel
better. Like one thing I heard a lot was
marriage is like a roller coaster.
And I disagree because roller coasters
are fun
[laughter]
and uh you can get off them.
I could never get off in my marriage.
[laughter]
I uh didn't realize what a coward I was
until I knew I wanted to get a divorce
and didn't know how to tell my
ex-husband.
So, I just started saying really
ambiguous [\h__\h]
I would look at the sky and be like, "I
should have been an astronaut."
[laughter]
And he was like, "What?" And I was like,
"I just love space.
>> [laughter]
>> It's like, "What?" And I was like, "I'm
moving out." [laughter]
>> So, I did. And I uh I live alone now,
which I love. [cheering]
>> Yes. [applause]
Does anyone here live alone?
[cheering]
[applause]
We could go rob almost all of you right
now.
No one is home.
I uh I love living alone, but it's a
little scary, right? I uh was eating the
other day and I was like, "Oh my god, if
I choke,
that's it.
No one's going to be here to see me
come.
[laughter]
What a waste.
So anyway, I'm in therapy.
Anyone here in therapy?
>> Yeah. Is it working?
>> No.
No. I think everyone should go. I don't
think anyone should expect results,
right? It's just a lot more work than
you would think. I think therapy is like
taking your car to the mechanic and
you're like, "The headlight's out. Just
fix that really quick." And then the
mechanic comes back and they're like,
[sighs]
>> [laughter]
>> There's a nest of rats in the engine,
and the rats are always your family.
[laughter]
But I was with my therapist the other
day, and she said the most insane thing
she's ever said to me. She said,
"Brittney, how about the next person you
[\h__\h] you try and love them?" [laughter]
I was like, "Whose [\h__\h] team are you
on?" [laughter]
So now I can't even masturbate.
[laughter]
[cheering]
>> [laughter]
>> That's a joke about how I hate myself.
[laughter]
I found out recently that I am
tragically straight.
Boo. Yeah. [laughter]
Yeah. Bad for the brand. I've
I've been telling people for over a
decade that I'm by. [laughter] Uh but it
turns out I was just a drunk.
And when I was drunk, I'd eat anything.
So,
I am sober now. Um,
[applause]
but if you guys don't laugh, I will
relapse
and leave with your wife. So, [laughter]
when I got divorced, my friends were
like, "Britney, who do you want to date?
What's the goal?" And I was like, "Oh,
that's easy." Like Idris Elba,
you know, I'd settle for Brad Pitt. And
they're like, "Okay, yeah, you're
shooting a little high." And I'm like,
"Well, you know what they say, shoot for
the moon. Even if you miss,
>> you'll [\h__\h] Nick Cannon. [laughter]
>> When you're young, you know you have
good [\h__\h] right?
>> [laughter]
>> I don't see anyone here young enough to
know. But
when it's fresh out the box, you're
like, I got that [\h__\h] I got that Z. I
got that fire.
[laughter]
I don't know what I got. I'll be honest.
I was in a relationship for seven years.
I don't know what's going on down there.
So now after I hook up with guys, I'm
like an annoying airline survey
afterwards. I'm like, "How was the
cleanliness?
How was the service?
How likely are you to recommend this to
your friends and family?" [laughter]
Cuz I'm trying to [\h__\h] your dad.
I was thinking about my [\h__\h] the other
day [laughter]
and I was like, "What's it like?" And I
think I got it. Uh, I think it's like a
Crunch Wrap Supreme. [laughter]
Everyone loves it.
It's better if you're drunk.
The meat's a little old
and eating it gives you cancer.
[laughter]
That's an HPV joke.
When I got divorced, I wanted to let
everyone know that I used to hook up
with that I was back in business. And uh
you know, when you eliminate everyone
that's married or had kids or died, uh
the pool was a little small, you know,
only like two
hundred. And so
I felt like a store that you used to
shop at reminding you that I'm still in
business. You know, it's like sent out a
blast email. I'm like, "Don't miss the
President's Day blow my backout sale.
Come on. Come on."
Now, I do feel like hooking up changes a
lot as you age, right? Like for me in my
20s, hooking up with me was like riding
a community scooter.
>> [laughter]
>> Anyone with a phone and $5 could do it.
But now I'm more like a classic car, you
know? Like it takes a lot to get me
started. [laughter]
Most of my value is sentimental.
[laughter]
And it's mostly just old guys taking me
for a ride in the summer.
>> [laughter]
>> Speaking of old guys, I went on a sugar
baby site recently.
>> Yeah. Woo. Uh,
no. And for those of you who don't know
what that is, that's, you know, young
girls date old guys for their money
pretty much. And, uh, when I went on
there, I learned very quickly, um, that
there's a real emphasis on baby in Sugar
Baby. You know, the guys on there were
like, I'm looking for someone 18 to 24
to see the world with. And I was like,
well, you're just saying that cuz it's
illegal to say 14 to 17. [laughter]
You don't need an app, you need a
playground.
[laughter]
I'll say this, it's a real dark day when
you realize you aged out of sex
trafficking.
>> [laughter]
>> I was like, I want to go to Dubai.
[laughter]
I'll keep my mouth shut.
No, but the nerve on these guys on this
site, there was a guy on there. He was
78 years old and his bio said, "I'm just
looking to settle down."
[laughter]
said, "Oh my god, do I have good news
for you?
You're about to settle down [laughter]
back into the earth, my guy.
[laughter]
You're going home, a r penis. [laughter]
Enjoy your last lap around the sun."
There was a guy on there that wanted to
send me flowers. Uh, so I gave him my
address and my friends got very mad at
me. [laughter]
They were like, "Britney, you're a
[\h__\h] idiot. Now this guy has your
address. He could kill you." And I was
like, "All right, so worst case
scenario,
I get flowers."
Have you guys ever considered suicide?
[laughter]
Well, if you haven't, now's a good time
to think about it. Uh,
no. I after my divorce, I was in a
really dark place and my ex-husband and
I are still friends. and we share a dog
and I went over to his place with the
dog and I was in a bad place and I laid
down on his floor and I started crying
and I was like, "This is just so hard. I
don't want to do this anymore." And he
was like, "Are you going to kill
yourself?" And I said, "I want to." And
he said, "You can't." And it's not
because I want you to live.
[laughter]
He said, "It's cuz so many people want
you dead." [laughter]
And I popped up off the ground. I was
like, "You're right, [\h__\h] I'm
staying in this [laughter] [\h__\h]
[applause]
I went on a date recently with a
bartender
cuz everything is going exactly as
planned." [laughter]
And after the date, he said to me, he
said, "I just want to tell you this now
so that there's no surprises later. I
don't believe in monogamy."
And I was like, "Oh, okay. Yeah, no,
that's going to be fine." Uh cuz I don't
believe in monogamy uh with a bartender.
[laughter]
And then he did something which changed
when I was married. People now tell each
other what they do in the bedroom before
they get in there. And back in my day,
we used to just get in there and get
surprised.
[laughter]
And every once in a while it was with a
fist. Um, [laughter]
but I think that's why they coined the
phrase, you just got to roll with the
punches, you know.
But he told me, he said, "I uh am a
pleasure dom, which means that I derive
pleasure from making my partner climax,
but I don't necessarily need to." And I
was like, "That sounds amazing.
[laughter]
In hindsight, it is the most elaborate
way anyone has ever told me they have an
erectile dysfunction. [laughter]
But silly me, I just believed him, you
know, and I had him come over and we
started hooking up and we were getting
hot and heavy and he was great at
foreplay, better than anyone I've ever
been with in my life. And I'm an adult.
When I'm horny, I want to [\h__\h] you
know? So, I'm trying to get a hold of
him and he's doing one of these
and I'm like, "Come to mama." [laughter]
And when I get him,
it's like an overcooked noodle,
[laughter]
like not even al dente. And I was like,
"What's this?" And uh he was like, "You
know, I just have to be honest with you.
I'm really sensitive to temperature
and your apartment doesn't have central
air. [laughter]
And I was so horny my brain broke.
[laughter]
I was like, the next morning I woke up
and I got approved for a home loan.
[laughter]
I was like, I must get this bartender
central air.
>> [laughter]
>> Do you know how horny you have to be to
get approved for a home loan? Like, it's
years of bank documents and tax
documents. And I don't know what you
guys know about the LA real estate
market, but if you have a million
dollars, you get a house with one thing.
You You either get a foundation or a
roof or central air. So, I went into
escrow on a house with just central air
and um
you know, I I had him come over when I
was in escrow again and then I found out
he just had you know, a run-of-the-mill
erectile dysfunction
cuz when we tried to hook up, it was
like putting Play-Doh in a piggy bank.
[laughter]
I was like, I'm gonna go ahead and pull
out of escrow because you're never gonna
pull out of me. [laughter]
After that, my friends were like,
Britney, you have to date young guys.
They keep their dicks hard. Uh, they
don't. [laughter]
I found one.
I started dating a pitcher for the
Angels. And by dating, I mean [\h__\h]
and
he's 8 years younger than me.
[cheering]
That is a big age gap, you know, like
when he was 12 and learning how to
spell, [laughter]
I was 20 and learning how to spell
CHLAMYIA
[applause]
cuz I had to legally let a few people
know they might have it.
But right before we went to hook up for
the first time, I just had an invasive
procedure done where I froze my eggs.
And afterwards, the doctor said to me,
he said, "Britney, you cannot have sex
for 2 weeks." Um, but you know how
sometimes doctors look you dead in the
eyes and they lie to you.
[laughter]
Like, I've had a doctor before be like,
"You cannot have 17 drinks in one
night."
>> [laughter]
>> And I'm like, "Have you met cocaine?"
Cuz yes, I can.
So, I go to hook up with this guy. We're
getting hot and heavy, and I think to
myself, I should probably tell him that
I can't have sex because I don't want to
leave my ovaries here tonight.
And in the time I have that thought, he
takes his pants off and his dick is 3 in
hard.
And for the first time in my life, I was
so excited to see a small dick.
I was like, would you look at God?
[laughter]
The Lord never gives you more than you
can handle. [laughter]
[cheering and applause]
And I was like, you can throw that thing
just about anywhere.
So he did. And here's the thing with
small dicks. Small dicks are like wagoo.
If you're gonna give me small portions,
they have to be really rich.
And if you don't understand that joke,
you're poor.
[applause]
No. The straw that broke the camel's
back for him and I as I went down to see
him in Orange County in the middle of
summer and he didn't have air
conditioning. [laughter]
And I know now it seems like this set
was brought to you by your local HVAC
guys, [laughter]
but what he had was way worse. He had
four fans. He had one above his bed, one
behind his bed, and one on either side
of his bed. [laughter]
So, while I'm down there sucking his
boowbo straw of a dick,
my hair was blowing around
like Beyonce in concert. [laughter]
I got up and I'm like, I'm a survivor.
[laughter]
I was like, hey man, what's up with the
fans? I was like, is it cuz you're an
athlete and you can't perform without
them?
>> [laughter]
>> and he didn't like that joke. And I was
like, "I'm just kidding. You play for
the Angels, you can't perform with
them." [laughter]
[cheering]
[applause]
And then as I was leaving, he said as
almost an afterthought, he was like,
"Hey, can I ask you a favor?" And I was
like, "Yeah, what's up?" He's like,
"Could you
like not write a joke about me?"
And I was like,
>> [laughter]
[gasps]
>> And then I left. And then
and then two weeks later, by the grace
of God, he got traded. Um yeah, he got
traded. And so you guys will never know
who this joke is about. Um
[laughter]
unless of course I told you he's the
lefty that just got traded to the Boston
Red Sox. [laughter]
You could probably figure it out.
When he did get traded, he got a really
big contract. And he is Mexican and he
doesn't have a relationship with his
dad. And when he got this really big
contract, I said to him, I said, "Hey,
if your dad doesn't come home with the
milk now, [snorts]
he's never coming home." [laughter]
And he looked at me and he's like,
"You're an [\h__\h]
You know that, right?" And I was like,
"No, that was culturally insensitive.
[laughter]
You're Mexican. It would be horada.
>> [laughter]
>> Speaking of angels,
my mom's dead
[laughter]
and she did kill herself. And
you guys not laughing at these jokes
won't bring her back to life. So, you
know, when life gets tough, people
always say, "Give it your best shot."
[laughter]
They got mad at her when she did.
She's a sharp shooter.
[laughter]
It's a one-dimensioned person here.
>> [applause]
>> The rest of you, congrats on your nice
childhood. You know, [laughter]
here's what I'll say you guys. I feel
you. I feel you getting really [\h__\h]
tight on me. Okay.
I don't care. But [laughter]
but what I will say is when you laugh, I
love that. That's my job to make you
laugh. When you guys get uncomfortable,
[laughter]
I LOVE [screaming] THAT.
>> [laughter]
[applause]
>> HERE'S THE THING ABOUT GRIEF. IF you've
ever lost somebody that you love, um,
you know grief is a [\h__\h] and it
hits you really hard and out of nowhere,
just like she did. [laughter]
>> [laughter]
>> Mom, they don't like these jokes about
you.
I'm just kidding. It's Mom, they don't
like these jokes about you.
[applause]
All right, you guys are not in the
minority. A lot of crowds get
uncomfortable when I do jokes about my
dead mom. Okay. [laughter]
Okay. I had a guy come up to me after a
show in DC and he said, "You know, it's
just really hard for me to hear you talk
about suicide because suicide is a
permanent solution to a temporary
problem." And I said, "Sir, if it helps
you sleep at night, just know my mom was
a permanent problem."
[cheering]
OKAY?
[applause]
That [\h__\h] woke up every day and chose
violence. You know, when I was in fourth
grade, I went to a Catholic school and I
played on the volleyball team. And my
mom had never played volleyball a day in
her life. And she volunteered to be the
volleyball coach
because that's how much she liked
yelling at kids.
She just did it for the love of the
game. You know, I was on the court.
There was a girl next to me. She's a
little heavier. Whatever. She missed the
ball. Who cares? My mom got in her grill
and she's like, "Move your feet, butter
ball."
And I sat there and I was like, "Jesus."
And the kids hated me because they're
like, "Your mom is a nightmare." And I'm
like, "This is her going out
personality.
This is this is as good as she gets, you
know?" And so I saw her I saw her life
every single day of her life was hell.
She never had a good day. And if that's
what's going on for you guys, you can
get out of here, you know, because
[laughter]
because it's not going to get better at
the end. And I will say
I will say when my mom did what she did,
I really really really
understood where her head was at.
[snorts]
[laughter]
It was all over the basement wall, you
guys.
Don't worry you guys, me and my mom are
good now.
That's my [\h__\h]
I'm 36 now, so I have to decide pretty
soon whether or not I want kids. And one
of the things that I have to consider is
that if I do have kids, I'm going to
have to tell them why their grandma's
not here and what happened. And that
sounds like a horrible conversation and
like one I don't really want to have at
all. So, what I've been doing um that's
been working great is just sending her
her grandkids so she can tell them
herself.
[cheering]
[applause]
That's an abortion joke.
>> [laughter]
>> And listen, if you didn't like it cuz
you're religious, um I would just like
to remind you that God did sacrifice his
only son. So I think he'd be fine with
it.
Growing up, uh we didn't have a lot. You
know, we had a small family. It was my
dad, my mom, my sister, and I. And uh we
didn't have a lot, but we did have each
other. And that was the worst part.
[laughter]
That was the worst part. My sister is a
year and nine months older than me and
100 times smarter than me. She is a
scientist
and she is trying to cure glaucoma.
[cheering]
[applause]
>> She won't,
[laughter]
but she can try. [laughter]
>> [gasps]
>> when she was getting her PhD, I told
everyone she was getting her PhD in
biochemical engineering because those
were the biggest words I knew.
And she called me and she said,
"Britney, you have to stop telling
people I'm getting my PhD in biochemical
engineering." And I said, "Why?"
She's like, "Cuz that's not what I'm
getting it in. I'm getting it in
cellular molecular immunology and
pathology."
I was like, "That feels like a bunch of
fake words.
[laughter]
You just made up to make me feel like a
[\h__\h] idiot." And my whole family's
stupid except except for my sister.
We're all dumb except for her. Like, we
have no idea what she does. At no point
have we ever had any idea. Like, we were
on a fishing trip last year and my back
hurt. And I was like, "If I lean
forward, it hurts. If I lean backwards,
it hurts." what is it? And she's like, I
don't know. And I was like, why do you
call yourself a doctor?
And then my dad caught a northern and
he's like, this is a kind of scary fish.
What do you think this evolved from? And
my sister's like, I don't know. And he's
like, why do you call yourself a
scientist? [laughter]
And then my mom, when she was alive, she
was obviously a blast.
[laughter]
And at the end of her life, she um had
paranoid schizophrenia and she thought
that the pharmacist was roofing her
Adavan.
So what she did is she put the Adavan in
a Nike shoe box and she duct taped it
shut and in Sharpie she wrote on the
box, "Heather, check for roofies. Love,
Mom."
And my sister called her panicking and
was like, "Mom, you sent this to my
school. That's not even what we do
here."
And my mom's like, "WHAT ARE THE LAB
CODES FOR?"
Our family is just a bunch of idiots.
And then my sister.
And 2020 was a really weird year for us
and only us. [laughter]
For those of you who blacked out, there
was a pandemic. And my sister was at
Duke working alongside the scientists
working on the vaccine.
And my dad is an antivaxer. [laughter]
So my sister dedicated her life to
science and my dad dedicated his to not
giving a [\h__\h] [laughter]
He's like, "My body, my choice." You
know, to be fair though, my dad does get
mad at both of us for what we put in our
bodies.
[laughter]
For her, it's Fizer. For me, it's black
guys.
[laughter]
Before I worked in comedy full-time, I
worked in corporate America and I worked
in advertising. And uh what happened in
2018 was the Me Too movement. So
basically before the Me Too movement,
you used to go into work and guys would,
you know, hit on you and act a little
inappropriately and it was pretty
gratuitous. And then after the Me Too h
movement happened, it stopped
immediately and
it was a little jolting, you know? It's
like not great for my self-esteem, you
know? [laughter]
I was like, "Come on, Harry. You [\h__\h]
pig. Give me something."
[laughter]
And maybe maybe I was getting ignored
because I worked in HR.
But I will say this, the Me Too movement
made me feel like a two.
[laughter]
I'll also say uh that feminists ruined
everything. [laughter]
No, my friends who are feminists are
like, "Don't you want the same amount of
money for the work that you're doing?"
And I'm like, "I don't want to work.
I don't want a job." Like, I feel like
our ancestors had it figured out
perfectly. They were just like high on
pills, neglecting kids, and cooking
casserles. I'm like, [laughter]
"Give me that life." You know, dreams
are for poor people.
If you guys think I'm bad at this job,
which some of you no doubt do, uh, just
know I was way worse at my other job.
I was the head of recruitment for a big
the biggest tech companies ad agency.
And um, what would you say is like the
worst thing you could do as a recruiter?
Does anyone have an idea?
>> Sleep with a candidate.
>> Sleep with a candidate. That was like my
sign on bonus. Um,
no. I would say the worst thing you
could do is what I did, um, which is
hire a murderer.
[laughter]
Whoopsie.
In my defense, uh, he hadn't been caught
yet,
but he did murder a woman in college and
then he buried her in his parents'
backyard and he got away with it for 23
years because he kept his mouth shut.
[sighs and gasps]
The position we were recruiting for was
an operations manager position, which
every year during black season, which is
like when the new technology came out,
um, this person needed to black out all
of the conference rooms and if they saw
any of the proprietary information in
there, they could not say anything.
In my defense, [laughter]
I feel like I got the best person for
the job, you know.
But what happened was um I was the head
of recruitment, so I wasn't in the weeds
doing the day-to-day recruitment. I had
junior recruiters beneath me, but I was
supposed to meet every single candidate
and look them in the eyes and make sure
they didn't murder somebody, you know.
But at the time, I was a drunk. And
my junior recruiter, she emailed me and
she said, "Hey, this guy is a little
creepy, but he really wants the job. Do
you want to meet him or should I just
give him the job offer?" And [snorts] I
responded,
"Don't worry." In writing. [laughter]
It was in writing. I said, "Just give
him the job offer and let's go get
margaritas.
And then what happened is he started
working there, you know, and everyone
was like, "This guy's [\h__\h] scary."
And they just they called him Scary
Paul. And I was like, "Well, they can't
all be winners, you know?"
And um
then a podcast came out called In Your
Own Backyard.
And I'm Listen, I'm not here to defend a
murderer. Not going to do that. But can
you guys imagine just for one minute
getting away with murder for 23 years
and then a nerd with a [\h__\h]
microphone [laughter]
gets on it and by the second episode he
was like, "It could only be one person.
It could only be Paul Flores." And I'm
like, "Ah,
[laughter]
fuck."
you know, and then um yeah, what
happened then was he got arrested. And
uh the worst part of this entire story,
aside from the fact that he did kill a
whole entire [\h__\h]
[laughter]
that when he got arrested, he was on the
cover of the New York Times in our
company t-shirt.
[applause]
[laughter]
I'm like, you always said hire a killer
candidate, you know? [laughter]
took it to the next level. No, thank God
I had quit that job already. Um because
if I hadn't, I would have been fired
because
they launched a huge, huge internal
investigation into, "Hey, how the [\h__\h]
did we hire a murderer?" [laughter]
And front and center was an email that
said, "Nah, just give him the job and
let's go get Margarita."
Oh my god. Okay, for this next joke, I
need a really, really big football fan.
Do we have one? [snorts]
[laughter]
>> Okay, that's enthusiastic. I can already
tell I'm not going to get what I need
out of you. But
who's your team?
>> Uh, the Panthers.
>> Panthers.
O.
>> All right. So, for this this joke, you
are gonna have to use all of your brain
power. [laughter]
Imagine the Panthers are in the Super
Bowl.
You going to faint? Okay. No, you're
good. Okay. So, imagine they're in the
Super Bowl and then they lose the Super
Bowl on a pass interference call. How
long do you stay mad for?
>> Couple months.
>> Couple months. Okay. So real football
fans will let this ruin their [\h__\h]
life. Like they they'll let it it's like
months, years, a whole lifetime. They'll
let it ruin everything. And for those of
you who don't watch football, um pass
interference is illegal touching and
guys get really mad about it. And I
think if guys got as mad about rape as
they did about pass interference,
[cheering]
[applause]
the world would be a better place, you
know? Cuz you should see these guys
after one of these calls. They're
walking around. They're like, "You can't
[\h__\h] touch them like that. You can't
just [\h__\h] do that. There's rules.
And we're sitting back there. We're
like,
[laughter]
that's what we've been saying. You know,
at no point are we like, well, what were
they wearing?
[laughter]
[applause] Were their pants a little
tight? [cheering]
[applause]
>> All right. I'm going to say one more
thing. and then I'm going to get out of
here. You guys have been an amazing
crowd. Make some noise for yourselves.
[cheering]
Thank you.
[applause]
I was [snorts] hooking up with a guy
recently. Surprise, surprise.
And he did something that I hate. He
started dirty talking.
And I can't do that because I'm too
honest, you know.
He started with a classic. He's like,
"Do you like this big dick, girl?
Do you like this big dick?" And I was
like,
"Yeah, I mean, it's average at best, but
you know, he was a white Jewish man. I
was
I was diversifying my portfolio, you
know."
And then what he said next is the most
insane thing I've ever heard in the
bedroom. He said, "Is this the biggest
dick you've ever had
in your entire life?"
And I fell apart. [laughter]
I started laughing,
which probably felt good physically,
[laughter]
not emotionally, but you know, I was
down there panicking. I'm like, how do I
tell this guy that I [\h__\h] the entire
NBA? Like,
how do I tell him that if his dick
casted a high noon shadow? That shadow
might be the biggest dick I've ever had
in my entire life.
Also, you don't go into the bedroom
asking questions you don't want answers
to, right? I would never go in there and
be like, "Is this the tightest little
[\h__\h] you've ever had in your entire
life?"
No, cuz it's not. And I know it's not
cuz every once in a while I feel a draft
up there. [laughter]
And it is the NBA draft.
>> [applause]
[cheering]
[applause]
>> Thank you so much, CHICAGO.
[cheering]
[applause]
>> [applause]
[cheering]
>> OKAY, you guys, before I go, I want to
do one more thing. Uh, for those of you
who don't know, this special is called
Sorry, Dad.
>> And my dad is here tonight. And I am so
sorry, Dad. [laughter]
So sorry you had to hear all of that.
Um, I want to bring him on stage really
quick and tell you guys a story. Are you
okay WITH THAT? [cheering]
>> [applause]
[cheering]
[applause]
>> IT'S ABOUT time she looked at me.
>> Okay, come up here. Come here, Faja. All
right, this is my dad. He is my
Charlie. This is Charlie. Do you want to
say anything?
>> I said it's about time she looked at me.
I couldn't look at him. Okay, so in a on
a serious note, my dad is my best
friend. He's the only person that's ever
loved me every day of my life. And he is
the person that taught me to laugh at
everything. And he he taught me that the
worse life gets, the funnier it also
gets. And [clears throat]
our life has been pretty funny.
But I will say this, this summer we had
a really bad health scare with my dad.
He had to get emergency quadruple bypass
surgery. And when he went in, he was
making all of the nurses laugh. And he
is just such an inspiration to me. And
when he came out, I've never seen
someone look worse. No offense.
[laughter]
He looked like he died two days ago. And
he had he had tubes hanging out of every
part of his body. And the second the
nurse pulled the tube out of his throat,
he looked up at her and he said, "Am I
going to be able to play guitar
and she said, "Yeah, you should be able
to." And he's like, "Well, that's cool
cuz I couldn't before.
MAKE SOME NOISE FOR CHARLIE SMITH.
[screaming]
[applause]
[cheering] HEAT. [applause]
[cheering]
[music]
HEAT. [cheering]
[cheering]
HEAT. [music]
[music]
HEAT.
[cheering]
[music]
>> [music]
[screaming]